Love can stand the test of time.
The Lost Valentine is a tv movie, romance, drama
film directed by Darnell Martin.
A young and cynical female journalist learns love may transcend trials and
time as she discovers a story that will change her life forever.
When war separates lovers on their wedding anniversary Feb.
14, 1944 at LA Union Train Station, Navy pilot Neil Thomas makes a promise he isn't sure he
can keep - to return to the train station safe by their next anniversary.
For sixty years Caroline Thomas keeps her promise by waiting at the train station until her missing in action husband can finally keep his
with the "lost valentine." The message and meaning shows romance and love can be real; worth fighting, and maybe even dying for.
Susan Allison, played by Jennifer Love Hewitt.
Caroline Thomas, played by Betty White.
Lucas Thomas, played by Sean Faris.
Neil Thomas, played by Billy Magnussen.
Young Caroline, played by Meghann Fahy.
Julie Oliver, played by Nadia Dajani.
The Lost Valentine is a 2011 drama film in the Hallmark Hall of Fame anthology
series starring Jennifer Love Hewitt, Betty White and Sean Faris.
It is based on the novel by James Michael Pratt of the same name, previously titled
The Last Valentine, a 1998 New York Times and USA Today bestseller.
In December 2011, Betty White received a nomination for the Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding
Performance by a Female Actor in a Miniseries or Television Movie for her performance.
The film explores themes of rescue, wheelchair, therapy, woman director.
The tone is emotional.